I’m hard to love, Jao.
[JAO] I’m ready to love you, Kara.
[JAO] No matter what.
Sir Han, why are you being so nice to me?
[KOREAN] I’m in love with you, Pearl.
I have been in love with you for the longest time.
And it pains my heart that I can’t tell you.
I didn’t understand anything.
You’ve been here a long time, huh?
I think I might stay here for good.
The curse got you, too!
You just don’t want to miss Kara.
Are you all set with your requirements?
Want to hear it?
This scholarship is not just an opportunity to study.
It's a chance for me to grow
and to honor the people who supported me.
[JEREMY] I just wanted to talk to you because…
I just wanted to check on you.
[JEREMY] You didn’t want to talk to me.
So, I wonder what changed your mind?
I finally decided that I wanted to move on.
Leaving you was the best decision I've ever made.
There’s something I’d like to discuss with you.
I got recruited by an international NGO.
Kara, I’d like you to take over for me.
[KARA] Remember Noah’s mangrove project?
- [JAO] Hm? - He wants to assign it to me.
- Wow, that’s amazing! - [KARA LAUGHS]
[JAO] I’m sure you’ll do great, Kara.
[CAROL GRUNTS]
[CAROL] Jeez...
- [CAROL] Busy day, huh? - Tell me about it.
What are we waiting for?
The go-signal.
It could come any time.
Manifesting.
- [CAROL] Let's deduct this because... - [PHONE RINGS]
Noah!
- [CAROL] It's Noah! - [PHONE CONTINUES RINGING]
[KARA BREATHES DEEPLY]
[PHONE CONTINUES RINGING]
Hello, Noah?
Good news?
[NOAH ON THE PHONE] It’s a go, Kara!
[NOAH ON THE PHONE] It's officially happening.
No way?
[NOAH ON THE PHONE] All thanks to you!
[NOAH ON THE PHONE] Where are we celebrating?
I’ll let you know!
Thanks!
[CAROL SHRIEKS AND LAUGHS]
[CAROL] Kara!
So many blessings!
You deserve them so much!
We’re celebrating, okay?
Absolutely! And guess what?
Jao’s boss approved his request to stay here, too.
- See? - Right?
We really deserve to celebrate.
[CAROL YELLS EXCITEDLY] Let’s go!
[CAROL] You know...
Isn’t the universe amazing?
- It always knows the perfect timing... - Don’t. You’re going to make me cry.
Hmm... It's just that...
- Remember when we first met? - [KARA] Yeah.
You were completely broken back then.
But now, so many good things are going on for you.
It’s all because of you guys.
- Oh. - [KARA] Especially you.
The best caregiver, the best cook,
the best at giving advice.
- The best sister. - [CAROL SQUEALS]
- Thanks, Carol. - I love you.
[KARA] Super thank you.
You deserve it, okay?
Enough drama.
- Let’s celebrate. - Come on.
- Your treat, of course. - I’ve got it covered.
Let’s go. Let's dance.
- Call your kids. - Okay.
Let’s go. GL?
- [KARA] Let’s go! - [CAROL GIGGLING AND LAUGHING]
[ALON BY JL]
- [CAROL SQUEALS] - [PEARL] Isn’t it nice here, Mom?
Of course.
- We’re here to celebrate Kara. - Yes!
They'll be here soon.
[SIARGAONON] The food here is amazing!
- Here? - Of course.
You have favorites here, right?
Yeah. For me, here, I love their sisig and kilaw.
- Yes. - Really delicious!
- [CAROL] They better be! Oh! - [PEARL] We ordered kilaw.
- Sir Noah! - Welcome, welcome!
- [HAN BIN] Welcome! - [ARIEL] You're with everyone. Hello!
- Glad you made it! - I wouldn't miss it.
Of course. How many are you?
- Four? Oh, make that five. - Four.
- Okay. Nice. - Let's go!
[CAROL YELLS EXCITEDLY] Thank you!
[PEARL] Ariel, didn’t you...
[WAITER] Sir, good evening.
[WAITER] I'm sorry, we have a private gathering tonight.
So we are closed.
[FOREIGNER] Seriously? We came all the way here,
now you’re telling us to leave?
Sorry about that, sir.
[PEARL] I thought it was Tuesdays.
- [ARIEL] Nope. Thursdays. - [PEARL] Really?
[ARIEL] Yeah.
- [ARIEL] It was Thursday. - [CAROL] Hold on.
- [ARIEL] What is he... - [CAROL] Jobel!
What’s going on?
- Why are they here? - I’ll check on the food.
I didn’t want to let them in. They pushed past me.
- [CAROL] What the heck? - [ARIEL] Han Bin oppa. I will show you…
Fine. Whatever!
We’ve got plenty of room. Just let them stay.
[SIARGAONON] It's fine.
- [ARIEL] Kilaw and sisig... - [CAROL] Jeez...
I’m really happy for you.
I’m already so proud that...
there’ll be more mangroves like Ruth on this island.
I'm also glad you're here to celebrate with me.
Thank you for staying.
Always.
[BACKGROUND CHATTER]
[CAROL] Noah! Noah!
[CAROL] Noah, do you want sisig?
[CAROL] Are you all okay with sisig? No allergies?
[CAROL] Okay. Kinilaw, too.
Adobo, too.
That looks good.
Nice. [PEARL LAUGHS]
I think they’d like…
um...
some juice.
Maybe pineapple juice.
Excuse me. Who are you?
Hi, there. I’m Santi.
Okay.
Come on. Don’t play hard to get.
Excuse me?
Out of all the Filipinas throwing themselves at me,
you’re lucky I even gave you attention!
I was looking...
- [CHAIR CLATTERS] - [CAROL] Hey!
...to make you my wife!
- But not anymore! - [PEOPLE GASP]
- [SANTI] Huh? - [HAN BIN] Hey! Stop!
Hey! What is...
[PEOPLE YELLING]
- [CAROL] Stop it! Stop it! - [GUESTS] Stop, stop, stop!
[PEARL] Sir Han!
[MUFFLED YELLING]
[MUFFLED] Get out of my way!
[JAO] Kara!
[YELLING CONTINUES]
- [ARIEL] Hey! Get out! - [CAROL] Stop this, everybody!
[SANTI] What's your problem?
Go home! Go home!
[CAROL] Stop this! Hey!
[MOTORCYCLE HORN HONKS]
[JAO] Watch where you’re going!
Kara!
- [ARIEL] Yes, take them away! - [CAROL] Take them to the barangay!
[ARIEL] Get them out of here!
- [CAROL] Unbelievable. - [ARIEL] Don’t come back here, okay?
[CAROL] Don’t come back! Leave us!
These are the guys they’re always talking about on the Siargao Community page!
I should post another complaint!
They can’t do that!
They’re just visitors, yet they’re the ones causing trouble?
Exactly!
They should be banned here so they won’t cause any more trouble.
[CAROL] My God!
Ariel…
thank you.
You were like a warrior princess there.
- [ARIEL] Please. - [CAROL ]It’s true.
For you and Mom, I’d fight anyone.
But I wasn’t your only protector.
I didn’t expect that to happen, actually.
[WAITER] Actually, I’m sorry for what happened to you.
Han Bin oppa.
[ARIEL] Look, those guys are notorious.
They’re all over our community page.
[CAROL] All of them!
[JAO] Kara?
[KARA] How’s Pearl?
[JAO] She’s okay.
How about you?
I just didn’t expect it to affect me the way it did.
I’m here to listen.
[KARA SIGHS]
Before I moved here,
I felt so trapped.
Jeremy and his parents...
they made me feel like I had no choice.
Like my feelings didn’t matter.
Because of them, I lost all confidence in myself.
It was…
the darkest moment of my life.
I thought I was okay.
I thought I’d moved on.
But…
What happened back there brought everything back.
Sir Han…
thank you for earlier.
You were so good.
You look like a K-drama actor.
[HAN BIN LAUGHS]
It’s okay. No need to thank me.
If it’s for you,
I don’t mind getting hurt.
- [HAN BIN GROANS] - Oh!
Sorry. I pressed too hard.
[PEARL AND HAN BIN LAUGH]
[HAN BIN EXHALES]
[PEARL CLEARS THROAT]
[PEARL AND HAN BIN LAUGH]
Ow!
- [PEARL LAUGHS] So... - [HAN BIN GROANS]
[PEARL LAUGHS] Sorry!
[PEARL AND HAN BIN LAUGH]
But you're here now, Kara.
Look at how far you’ve come.
You didn't let your past drown you out.
And you’re stronger now. Don’t forget that.
I just want you to know you’re not alone anymore.
I know it's hard for you to trust people, but I’m here now.
I’m here now.
I’m not going anywhere.
You’re safe with me, Kara.
Can you promise me one thing?
Promise me that...
even if you know I'll get angry,
or hurt, you'll still tell me the truth.
[JAO] I promise.
And I also promise...
that I'll never hurt you.
I love you, Kara.
[JAO] Beautiful. Like a painting.
This is better because it’s real.
And it’s right in front of our eyes.
This is the point of life.
[KARA] Watching the sun rise with the person you love.
- Good day, sir! - Hello.
- Checking in? - Yes.
[PEARL] Let me guess. Korean.
Very good guess.
Yes, because the owner of this hotel,
my boss, he’s Korean, too.
[KOREAN] Stop it now.
The guy you sent is trying to take me back!
Sir Han!
We have a Korean guest and he wants to meet you.
I know.
You’re expecting Sir Won?
[HAN BIN] Whatever happens, Pearl,
please know that everything that I’ve shown you was real.
Did something happen? Do I need to know anything?
There’s a lot of things I need to tell you,
but I never found the right opportunity.